{
  "Custom": {
     "q1": {
       "topic": "Basketball",
       "question": "Which one is correct team name in NBA?",
       "answer_a": "Brooklyn Pets",
       "answer_b": "Toronto Raptors",
       "answer_c": "Los Angeles Slackers",
       "answer_d": "Memphis Bearcubs",
       "correct_answer": "b",
       "hint": "We the North"
     },
     "q2": {
       "topic" : "Algorithms",
       "question": "What is the best-case time complexity of bubble sort?",
       "answer_a": "n^2",
       "answer_b": "n*log(n)",
       "answer_c": "n*log(n)^2",
       "answer_d": "n",
       "correct_answer": "d",
       "hint": "started from the bottom"
     },
     "q3": {
       "topic" : "Algorithms",
       "question": "Which of the following sorting algorithms has the lowest worst-case complexity?",
       "answer_a": "merge sort",
       "answer_b": "bubble sort",
       "answer_c": "quick sort",
       "answer_d": "selection sort",
       "correct_answer": "a",
       "hint": "don't merge into oncoming traffic"
     },
     "q4": {
       "topic" : "Algorithms",
       "question": "Which of the following is not a stable sorting algorithm in its typical implementation?",
       "answer_a": "insertion sort",
       "answer_b": "merge sort",
       "answer_c": "quick sort",
       "answer_d": "bubble sort",
       "correct_answer": "c",
       "hint": "think fast"
     },
     "q5": {
       "topic" : "Algorithms",
       "question": "Which one of the following in-place sorting algorithms needs the minimum number of swaps?",
       "answer_a": "quick sort",
       "answer_b": "selection sort",
       "answer_c": "insertion sort",
       "answer_d": "heap sort",
       "correct_answer": "b",
       "hint": "select an answer"
     },
     "q6": {
       "topic" : "Algorithms",
       "question": "Let T be a depth first search tree in an undirected graph G. Vertices u and n are leaves of this tree T. The degrees of both u and n in G are at least 2. which one of the following statements is true?",
       "answer_a": "there must exist a vertex w adjacent to both u and n in G",
       "answer_b": "there must exist a vertex w whose removal disconnects u and n in G",
       "answer_c": "there must exist a cycle in G containing u and n",
       "answer_d": "there must exist a cycle in G containing u and all its neighbors in G",
       "correct_answer": "d",
       "hint": "love thy neighbor"
     },
     "q7": {
       "topic" : "Algorithms",
       "question": "Let A1, A2, A3, and A4 be four matrices of dimensions 10 x 5, 5 x 20, 20 x 10, and 10 x 5, respectively. The minimum number of scalar multiplications required to find the product A1A2A3A4 using the basic matrix multiplication method is",
       "answer_a": "1500",
       "answer_b": "2000",
       "answer_c": "500",
       "answer_d": "100",
       "correct_answer": "a",
       "hint": "one hundred quinceaneras"
     },
     "q8": {
        "topic": "Data Structures",
        "question": "Which one of the following is an application of the stack data structure?",
        "answer_a": "managing function calls",
        "answer_b": "the stock span problem",
        "answer_c": "artithmetic expression evaluation",
        "answer_d": "all of the above",
        "correct_answer": "d",
        "hint": "go above the call of duty"
      },
      "q9": {
        "topic": "Data Structures",
        "question": "The best data structure to check whether an arithmetic expression has balanced parenthesis is a",
        "answer_a": "queue",
        "answer_b": "list",
        "answer_c": "tree",
        "answer_d": "stack",
        "correct_answer": "d",
        "hint": "the odds are stacked against you"
      },
      "q10": {
        "topic": "Data Structures",
        "question": "To implement Dijkstra’s shortest path algorithm on unweighted graphs so that it runs in linear time, the data structure to be used is",
        "answer_a": "stack",
        "answer_b": "queue",
        "answer_c": "b-tree",
        "answer_d": "heap",
        "correct_answer": "b",
        "hint": "right on cue"
      },
      "q11": {
        "topic": "Data Structures",
        "question": "A list of n strings, each of length n, is sorted into lexicographic order using the merge sort algorithm. The worst case running time of this computation is",
        "answer_a": "O(n*log(n))",
        "answer_b": "O(n^2*log(n))",
        "answer_c": "O(n^2 + log(n))",
        "answer_d": "O(n^3)",
        "correct_answer": "b",
        "hint": "you'll be sorry"
      },
      "q12": {
        "topic": "Data Structures",
        "question": "Suppose that we have numbers between 1 and 1,000 in a binary search tree and want to search for the number 364. Which of the following sequences could not be the sequence of nodes examined?",
        "answer_a": "925, 221, 912, 245, 899, 259, 363, 364",
        "answer_b": "926, 203, 912, 241, 913, 246, 364",
        "answer_c": "3, 400, 388, 220, 267, 383, 382, 279, 364",
        "answer_d": "3, 253, 402, 399, 331, 345, 398, 364",
        "correct_answer": "b",
        "hint": "i'm feeling lucky"
      },
      "q13": {
        "topic": "Data Structures",
        "question": "Consider a binary max-heap implemented using an array. Which one of the following array represents a binary max-heap?",
        "answer_a": "25, 12, 16, 13, 10, 8, 14",
        "answer_b": "25, 12, 13, 10, 16, 8, 14",
        "answer_c": "25, 14, 16, 13, 10, 8, 12",
        "answer_d": "25, 14, 12, 13, 10, 8, 16",
        "correct_answer": "c",
        "hint": "the most popular vitamin"
      }
  }
}